https://www.aviation24.be/privacy-policy/

Home Active topics COVID-19 Forums
New posts Latest aviation news Airline experiences and trip reports Civil aviation / General aviation Military aviation Plane spotting forums Website related
Latest news
Airlines Airports Manufacturers
Search Shop Top 24 Trip reports
Sign in
Welcome!Log into your accountyour usernameyour password
Forgot your password?Privacy policy
Password recovery
Recover your passwordyour email
Search
1.1 C
Brussels
11 December 2020About Advertise Contact Jobs Join Login Forums Newsletter Stats Travel FR
Sign inWelcome! Log into your accountyour usernameyour password
Forgot your password? Get helpPrivacy policy
Password recoveryRecover your passwordyour email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Aviation24.be
Home Active topics COVID-19 Forums
New posts Latest aviation news Airline experiences and trip reports Civil aviation / General aviation Military aviation Plane spotting forums Website related
Latest news
Airlines Airports Manufacturers
Search Shop Top 24 Trip reports
Home
Privacy policy
Privacy policy
Who we are
Our website address is: http://www.aviation24.be, read our about-page for more information. This website is hosted at the Nucleus.be data center, holding an ISO 27001 certificate for data protection.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Forums
If you leave a message in our forums we collect the data shown in the forum message, and also the member’s IP address and browser user agent string.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
If you contact us via the contact form we collect the data shown in the comment box, your name, your email address and also your IP address to help spam detection. We will keep your contact form submission as long as deemed necessary, we will not use the information submitted through for marketing purposes.
Daily newsletter
If you subscribe to our daily newsletter we add your email address to our mailing list at Mailchimp, we will not use your email address for marketing purposes. At all time you are able to unsubscribe from this list.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
When using our forums the phpBB software will create a number of cookies, the first two cookies just contain a user identifier (hereinafter “user-id”) and an anonymous session identifier (hereinafter “session-id”), automatically assigned to you by the phpBB software. A third cookie will be created once you have browsed topics within our forums and is used to store which topics have been read, thereby improving your user experience.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
This site does not share any personal data with anyone.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
If you leave a message in our forums, the message and its metadata are retained indefinitely.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments and/or posted messages in our forums, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
If your forum message doesn’t comply with our forum rules, website administrators will change and/or remove your forum message.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Aviation24.be (luchtzak.be)
BE 0677.418.306
Kriekelaarstraat 30
1981 Hofstade
Belgium
+32 (0)475/25.44.11 (Bart Noëth)
Password
Your password is ciphered (a one-way hash) so that it is secure. However, it is recommended that you do not reuse the same password across a number of different websites. Your password is the means of accessing your account on our site, so please guard it carefully and under no circumstance will anyone affiliated with Aviation24.be, phpBB or another 3rd party, legitimately ask you for your password. Should you forget your password for your account, you can use the “I forgot my password” feature provided by the phpBB software. This process will ask you to submit your user name and your email, then the phpBB software will generate a new password to reclaim your account.
Additional information
How we protect your data
We maintain certain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to help protect against loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of your personal data. In the first place, this is about firewalls. In addition, there’s 24/7 monitoring and Intrusion Prevention & Intrustion Detection System (IPS/IDS) as well. As an extra, we also offer DDoS protection. More information: Nucleus.be security measures.
Personal data breaches can include:
Access by an unauthorised third party;
Deliberate or accidental action (or inaction) by a controller or processor;
Sending personal data to an unintended recipient;
Lost or stolen computing devices containing personal data;
Unauthorised alteration of personal data; and
Loss of availability of personal data.
What data breach procedures we have in place
Every violation of our security (a.k.a. a data breach) that involves personal data is reported to every involved member of this site, and this as soon as possible;
Every violation of our security (a.k.a. a data breach) that involves personal data is reported to the authorities (in Belgium that’s the privacy commission) within 72 hours.
Akismet (anti-spam measure)
We collect information about visitors who comment on Aviation24.be which uses our Akismet anti-spam service. The information Akismet collects includes the commenter’s IP address, user agent, referrer, and Site URL (along with other information directly provided by the commenter such as their name, username, email address, and the comment itself).
Last update: 28 May 2018
Aviation24.be latest
Aviation industry welcomes European Commission’s Sustainable and Smart Mobility Strategy as it readies decarbonisation roadmap
André Orban -
10 December 2020 0
Transporting the COVID-19 vaccine, Amsterdam Airport Schiphol is getting ready
André Orban -
10 December 2020 0
Oxford researchers partner with American Airlines, British Airways and oneworld to analyse COVID-19 testing trials results
André Orban -
10 December 2020 0
airBaltic announces summer 2021 schedule: 65 destinations, including 5 new ones
André Orban -
10 December 2020 0
Chinese aviation authority CAAC recommends cabin crew to wear disposable diapers for COVID-19 protection
Bart Noëth -
10 December 2020 0
Aviation24.be trending
Antonov Airlines puts giant An-225 Mriya aircraft into commercial operation as demand for heavy-lift capacity surges
André Orban -
7 December 2020 0
Suspicious situation onboard an aircraft at Amsterdam Schiphol, passengers evacuated
Bart Noëth -
9 December 2020 1
Nine people complained 17,000 times about noise disturbance caused by Amsterdam Schiphol – in 1 year
Bart Noëth -
9 December 2020 0
Norwegian initiates reorganisation process in Norway
André Orban -
8 December 2020 0
One arrest after bomb threat on KLM Boeing 737 at Amsterdam Schiphol
Bart Noëth -
10 December 2020 2
Latest forum topicsCivil aviation / General aviation • new beluga xl 10 December 2020 lomcovakLatest aviation news • Brussels Airlines in 2020 10 December 2020 nordikcamPlane spotting - Belgium • BRU 10/12/2020 10 December 2020 sdbelgiumPlane spotting - Belgium • ANR 10/12/2020 10 December 2020 sdbelgiumLatest aviation news • BRU Winter 2020-2021: news, new routes, airlines 10 December 2020 longwingsLatest aviation news • Impact of the coronavirus crisis on aviation 9 December 2020 sn26567Latest aviation news • Boeing 737 (MAX) news 9 December 2020 sn26567Plane spotting - Belgium • EBCV 10/12/2020 9 December 2020 tangolimaPlane spotting - Belgium • CRL 10/12/2020 9 December 2020 tangolimaMilitary aviation • 9 ship Eurofighter Typhoon Flypast from the Royal Air Force at RAF Fairford 9 December 2020 MUC-SpotterFacebookAviation24.be
Calendar December 2020
M T W T F S S
123456
78910111213
14151617181920
21222324252627
28293031
« Nov
Daily newsletterJoin 748 other newsletter subscribers and receive a daily update of airline news and latest press releases!
We protect your data, read our privacy policy.Leave this field empty if you're human: Meta
Privacy & cookies: Aviation24.be uses cookies. To find out more, see our
cookies policy
Abuse Advertise Contact us Cookies policy Hosting Privacy policy News team Webteam Welcome on aviation24.be
© Copyright 2001-2020 - Aviation24.be - FKA Luchtzak.be
